govtnaukri.org 2015-02-18

# Privacy Policy - Government Jobs India

The privacy of our visitors to **Govtnaukri.org** is very important to us.

At  **Govtnaukri.org** we are committed to protect your privacy during your visits to our website and we  recognize that privacy of your personal information is important . Here is the l information we receive and collect when you use and visit **Govtnaukri.org .  ** We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies  and Web Beacons**

Cookies are small text files placed on your computer and are commonly used on the internet **We use them to  ** collect anonymous information that will help us understand visitors’ browsing habits on our website; > compile statistical reports on website activity, e.g. number of visitors and the pages they visit; Note: We do not use cookies to track your use of the internet after you leave our sites, nor do we store any personal information in them that others could read and understand.

We also use third party advertisements on **Govtnaukri.org**  to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers  information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. We do not use cookies to track your use of the internet after you leave our sites, nor do we store any personal information in them that others could read and understand

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history .  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as Other Jobs websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**Disclaimer** : This site is not responsible for publishing all available jobs as well accuracy, neither are we related to Indian government or any of its subsidiaries. please check posted jobs with its original sources, e.g. News Papers/ Websites etc..

**NEED TO CONTACT US ?**

Kindly mail us at info@govtnaukri.org  we will be happy to be at your service.

## **ARE YOU INTERESTED IN ADVERTISING IN OUR WEBSITE ?**

Mail us at advertise@govtnaukri.org
